<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Digital Productivity Coach</title>
    <link>https://digitalproductivity.coach/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Digital Productivity Coach</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2019 James Stuber</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://digitalproductivity.coach/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://digitalproductivity.coach/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalproductivity.coach/about/</guid>
      <description>About The Digital Productivity Coach was built by productivity nerds Tasshin Fogleman and James Stuber.
Colleagues, clients, and friends were asking both of us for productivity tips. While we&amp;rsquo;re happy to teach, one-on-ones are time consuming and hard to schedule.
We searched for a single, easy-to-use resource to share with others, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t find one. Instead of giving up, we built our own: The Digital Productivity Coach.
Tasshin Fogleman Tasshin is the Assistant Director at the Monastic Academy in Lowell, VT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ali Abdaal</title>
      <link>https://digitalproductivity.coach/ali/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalproductivity.coach/ali/</guid>
      <description>An interactive coach for digital productivity, available 24&amp;frasl;7 to give you a feasible next step to improve your productivity skills.
👋 Hello Ali Abdaal viewers! Thanks for checking out the Digital Productivity Coach!
🎓 Students If you&amp;rsquo;re a student who watches Ali Abdaal, follow this link to try out the Digital Productivity Coach, free of charge
Get the Digital Producitivity Coach If you have the means, a purchase is greatly appreciated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Digital Productivity Coach</title>
      <link>https://digitalproductivity.coach/the-digital-productivity-coach/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalproductivity.coach/the-digital-productivity-coach/</guid>
      <description>An interactive coach for digital productivity, available 24&amp;frasl;7 to give you a feasible next step to improve your productivity skills.
&amp;ldquo;I constantly try new apps and tools to get organized and yet I never get anything done!&amp;rdquo; If you want to level up your productivity, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to feel overwhelmed.
There are dozens of systems and tools and acronyms and it all sounds so complicated.
You read blog post after blog post, waiting for some kind of &amp;ldquo;a-ha!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>